Finding Aid for Men's Glee Club (University of Michigan) records 1886-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- China Concert Tour, 2012
  - Shanghai (May 13 to May 16, 2012)
    - Yu Yuan Garden, May 14, 2012
      - Digital images of the Men's Glee Club visit to Yu Yuan Garden
- Archived Website
  - Archived Men's Glee Club website, 2011-[ONGOING]